[{"question":"<p>The glory of the Gothic Cathedrals is their<\/p>","options":["use of colour marbels","simple architectural rendering","use of magnificent stained glass","complex architectural rendering"],"answerIndex":3,"examYear":"2018"},{"question":"<p>Dyes are colourants most suitable for<\/p>","options":["printing on fabrics","painting on walls","drawing on canvas","printing on papers"],"answerIndex":1,"examYear":"2018"},{"question":"<p>In traditional Nigerian art, there is a cultural and artistic connection between<\/p>","options":["Nok and Ife","Benin and Igala","Nok Benin","Ife and Benin"],"answerIndex":1,"examYear":"2018"},{"question":"<p>The first tertiary institution in Nigeria to have an art curriculum was<\/p>","options":["Yaba College of Technology, Lagos","Institute of Management Technology, Enugu","University of Nigerua, Nsukka","Ahmadu Bello University, Zaria"],"answerIndex":1,"examYear":"2018"},{"question":"<p>In lettering one of the principles is that round characters are placed<\/p>","options":["apart","closely","at an angle","overhead"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"2018"},{"question":"<p>Prehistoric cave paintings reflected<\/p>","options":["animals","building","plants","people"],"answerIndex":1,"examYear":"2018"},{"question":"<p>Captions used to enhance television announcements would be more understandable if produced as<\/p>","options":["collage","graphics","painting","mosaics"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"2018"},{"question":"<p>Which of the following does a textile artist use to form patterns?<\/p>","options":["motif","posters","yam","logo"],"answerIndex":1,"examYear":"2018"},{"question":"<p>In Nigerua, thorn carving is practised in<\/p>","options":["Shagamu and Oshogbo","Owo and Ado -Ekiti","Ado-Ekiti and Ilesha","Owo and Shagamu"],"answerIndex":4,"examYear":"2018"},{"question":"<p>A spatula can be inprovised using<\/p>","options":["feather","wood","charcoal","clay"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"2018"},{"question":"<p>An armature is essential to the artists in executing large works in<\/p>","options":["ceramics","craft","sculpture","carving"],"answerIndex":3,"examYear":"2018"},{"question":"<p>Varninsh is essential for the protection of<\/p>","options":["water colour painting","pastel painting","oil painting","gouache painting"],"answerIndex":3,"examYear":"2018"},{"question":"<p>Dogo of Mali is renown for its<\/p>","options":["textile","masks","engravings","decorations"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"2018"},{"question":"<p>In computer graphics the name given to a device used in navigating the window environment is<\/p>","options":["pencil","ruling pen","keyboard","mouse"],"answerIndex":4,"examYear":"2018"},{"question":"<p>Byzantine art emerged in the 4thcentury in<\/p>","options":["Constantinople","Crete","Rome","Paris"],"answerIndex":1,"examYear":"2018"},{"question":"<p>The use of lines to describe an object is known as<\/p>","options":["drawing","pottery","painting","graphics"],"answerIndex":1,"examYear":"2018"},{"question":"<p>Which of the following pigments can be obtained locally from clay?<\/p>","options":["lemon yellow","yellow ochre","green","blue"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"2018"},{"question":"<p>Pointillism become more popular during<\/p>","options":["the Renaissance","Modern Art","Classicsm","Impressionism"],"answerIndex":4,"examYear":"2018"},{"question":"<p>Which of the following is best arranged in order of softness?<\/p>","options":["2B, H and 3B","3B, 2B, H and HB","H, HB, 2B and 3B","3B, HB, H and 2B"],"answerIndex":3,"examYear":"2018"},{"question":"<p>Which of the following is regarded as the founder of Nigerian museums?<\/p>","options":["Kenneth Murray","William Faggs","Jimoh Akolo","Ben Enwonwu"],"answerIndex":1,"examYear":"2018"},{"question":"<p>In the pictorial composition given, the eye level is represented by line<\/p>","options":["GH","KL","EF","IJ"],"answerIndex":3,"examYear":"2018"},{"question":"<p>If the shape illustrated above is a mould, which of the following will best fit into it?<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>i.<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p><img src=\"data:image\/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAAGgAAABOCAYAAADM6VOKAAABKklEQVR4nO3XQWrDMABFQd3\/0u4iBEpphLNo9RTNA++88NeAsceldGP1A2geoHiA4gGKBygeoHiA4gGKBygeoHiA4gGKBygeoHiA4gGKBygeoHiA4gGKlwYaI\/14\/1L6BAAtABpj3Dr4u\/d9ektO4Hn4M4A795zQsvXfAX5DAPRo6foZEqBHKaDZdWrLlwOal1gO6XWJ1e+86k6DSqx9F+gkqG0+Ek4FW\/6j+hfXJ7V8DZx5uUWng\/wsu\/B0mGfppYDiQNf1GumUtlgKaIMAxQO0QScibbcS0AYB2iBAG3QC0ucv3DxA8QDFAxQPUDxA8QDFAxQPUDxA8QDFAxQPUDxA8QDFAxQPUDxA8QDFAxQPUDxA8QDFAxQPUDxA8QDFAxQPUDxA8QDF+wKsm+baRtwgogAAAABJRU5ErkJggg==\" \/><\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>ii.<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p><img src=\"data:image\/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAAEIAAABFCAYAAAD+UTBQAAAA9ElEQVR4nO3Xyw7CMAwFUf\/\/T5sFk\/KQKgTUiavOrIHrnB2RlpmZsfqALglBQpAQJAQJQUKQECQECUFCkBC0HCJi+QmZuRgiIoTIfEB0wBBi3LJ0XIhXBCGEEOI++obQAUOIcdO0oZ3HdwEpWf3m0V1gylaOxqgGEWLcW\/rjJwDYbp0y0hhgu3HKiBBPQ00BtvumDQnB0M6DLwXx6bEdMJZA\/PqZyoQY++UDXzzwMhAVnz+qaRDV3\/m38v8aZ0kIOs+lxQlBQpAQJAQJQUKQECQECUFCkBAkBAlBQpAQJAQJQUKQECQECUFCkBAkBAlBQpAQdAPM1C+N6UyWZAAAAABJRU5ErkJggg==\" \/><\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>iii.<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>&nbsp;<img src=\"data:image\/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAAEEAAAA5CAYAAABphkbpAAAA4klEQVRoge3X0QrDIAwFUP\/\/p8+eOsYYG11NjXAv+GQoyUHEDomxuoEOCYIgIAgIAoKAICAICAKCgCAgCAgCgoAgIAgIAoKAYoQxhjH6O9+C0B0iCCYjfBp6B4jpnb0O\/b66pqSz3SCCoPBi3AliCcKvdXeC4ALClSE7ATDpJOwMQOFjaYfhn31P\/dhmwx+Z1smOJ+DI0juhS4JgAsLZoTtCXOri20D\/7q3IlMdSxf6dKf+LnFFXnaUIr7UrU4pwpn5lWiCszj6dFiYIgoAgIAgIAoKAICAICAKCgCAgCAgCeADCx\/r8B1X\/5wAAAABJRU5ErkJggg==\" \/><\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>iv.<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>&nbsp;<img src=\"data:image\/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAAEgAAABHCAYAAACkuwGSAAAEjUlEQVR4nO3Y\/0\/UZQDAcf8JOdgd97nDQ8tpfsEvCYZmI50uaKSzudaipcuRGYqIX\/rByvyCyNxFFKYg4ixbfunLKqqVk1Wb1oZoCQjmgQsGWyF3HNx9nufdD4CBBzzUvLuk5709P9xttz332vN5ns\/nMwHdqE2I9gT+62kgRRpIkQZSpIEUaSBFGkiRBlKkgRRpIEUaSJEGUqSBFGkgRRpIkQZSpIEUaSBFGkiRBlKkgRRpIEURA5JSDh2ibwhTIIWM1DT+cREDEkLg9\/vxer00NTVx6eJFXt+1i3dKimlu9iClRAiBlEOxTNMkEAiEfB+pInqJDSAIIfB6u8hev45tWzfTeL0eIUzq6q7R0FCP3+8P+c3\/AmggKSVXai+zKjODFUvTuHD+O253\/sHO7XmUFLvxer3RmNawRQ2ovOwIKQvm4nIanDhewfGKMhanJlNUWEBX1+1oTGvYogAkCQYCvLwhG5czHsMWyzNrVrM0bQmO+DgKC\/bR2fln5Kc1QlEBqq\/7lVWZGRg2C4bNgiM+FsNmwW6NoehgAV5vV+SnNUJR2aQ\/PPU+jz6SfAdoMFRJsZve3t5ITmvUInofJITgl6u1PPfsGhIT7CFAhtXC228doqfH339yDQwJUoL8+34qUoUVaPCNYXe3j4pj5SxcMBe7NSYEx26NwbDGMC9pBk+vXsn6F9eSm5tDYeF+jh49THnZe5SXHebTT87R0twcMaSwA3V3d\/PxuTOkL1+Gy2HHsMWGrpzBUMMNq4XJLicrM5\/k5IlK2lp\/vz+BpJSYpklHRwfnv\/2Ggwf2sTg1mUmGFcPadwmNhtM3YvpXU9\/n2TOmkrMxmx9\/+J5gIHjnpvG+BfJ4PGRlZbEoNYWU5HkkuhzYB19GYwSaM2s6e\/e8wc2bNzDNAFKKeznVMXfPL7E7jxPSRIgg7e1tfHCygtVPpfNAomNMQFNcdt4tcWOaQQQggGg9zoYF6O4hpCBo9lJx7AgpDycpgQybhfXrnufqlcuYQiCkHB9AUkp6enpC9gcBBIMB3IeKmJv00JCTa2DcfaK5nDa2b8vD4\/FE7UEVwgAkROheIYAbvzXxxIplQ\/ajyZPsbH4lm88\/O8uB\/btZuGAOxiCs+fOSqKysHD9AIxXo7SF\/yyamTUnAYZ2IMz6OtS9kUV19AZ\/PB\/Th1tTUsHPHdubPmYlhm4jTbmHnjjza29vG9+uOr6uqWLwwGUf\/0b0lN4fGxush73mklASDQb6q+pKM9OXYrTGkLUnl7JmPhl2ZkSjsN4pCCDZueIkHExNw2uJ4c\/drtNxqGXHjHfhNff01Xt2xldmzppGfn0dbW2tUVlHYgRoaGnj8sUXMnD6Vgr17uNXSMubV4PN1cfr0KfLzc6mq+iIqbxbDDuR2u9mUs5Gff7pEb\/8JN9Y\/KaVACJPq6guUlpZSW1s7\/oBaW1vx+byYpvmv\/9zgd9njCmg8pIEUaSBFGkiRBlKkgRRpIEUaSJEGUqSBFGkgRRpIkQZSpIEUaSBFGkiRBlKkgRRpIEUaSJEGUqSBFGkgRRpIkQZS9BcxIq77IeARNgAAAABJRU5ErkJggg==\" \/><\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>&nbsp;&nbsp;<\/p>","options":["i","ii","iii","iv"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"2018"},{"question":"<p>Which of the following are characteristics of Egyptian arts?<\/p>","options":["Rigidity and frontality","use of bright and raw colours","short feet and small thighs","roundness of shoulder"],"answerIndex":1,"examYear":"2018"},{"question":"<p>An atomizer is most ideal in the application of<\/p>","options":["fixative","polymer","linseed oil","poster colours"],"answerIndex":1,"examYear":"2018"},{"question":"<p>Wood carving in Yorubaland was primarily meant for<\/p>","options":["royalty","economic purpose","ceremony","religious purpose"],"answerIndex":4,"examYear":"2018"},{"question":"<p>i.&nbsp; <img src=\"data:image\/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAAFcAAABhCAYAAACj6z3cAAABf0lEQVR4nO3XUWrDMBAGYd0fesFcRn0pRrg21CGj\/aXOgF+9ux8h4NYNq1UvsHPigokLJi6YuGDigokLJi6YuGDigokLJi6YuGDigokLJi6YuGDigokLJi6YuGDigokLJi6YuGDigokLJi6YuGDigokLJi6YuGDigi2D21q7fJLL3u6nO9h05Mythv4Cmwqct9HQE1hxH\/YUNw04a5tT4oKJCyYunLhwqwLnbHLRO38LSdBxuJ8ATcGOwaVRK5AjcGfDzgIux62CnQFcilsNSwOX4VaDbotbjSnuBsDTcasRxRX3zYEBkDNgexd3L9zes4DRO9G33w0NQKVhe\/\/HHxFTbpwy5W74pqjHfVOnXS2wIepxW8nUU7uhHneVTj+1A+hYziZDK4OOZW7V+y+0FTDPrbHlookLJi6YuGDigokLJi6YuGDigokLJi6YuGDigokLJi6YuGDiUr2+xCUTF0xcMHHBxAUTF0xcMHHBQNwX9+pF8pcLJi6YuGDign0DzfCUYk98EEwAAAAASUVORK5CYII=\" style=\"height:95px; width:85px\" \/>&nbsp;&nbsp; ii. <img src=\"data:image\/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAAFIAAABLCAYAAADj9dDIAAABV0lEQVR4nO3ZwQ6CMBAA0f7\/T9eTxhiJirPbXTqTcPAALS8kFjqmIY3VE7hKQkIJCSUklJBQQkIJCSUklJBQQkIJCSUklJBQQkIJCSUkVGvIMcbjWN36GZzsGbACZmvI198rMVtCHqGtxGwH+QlrFWYryG+RVmC2gfwVR8g3nX3CMjHbQJ49LwuzPOS\/GFmYpSEphAzMspD0zUdjloSMuunId\/NykOFPzk6QGWPQ45SCTF2uXBlyzrxFtJDQGEJCY2wBGb543uFfe86cJRB+TfyKQJGQ26wj70W+3US0FWTokx5yVaiIDxdRlYacs8+ntPKQc\/b4uNsKsvKWQwvIe2dA3Go46Ne9bTe\/PvQMdXSkzid1tKBWAj7msGTUCyYklJBQQkIJCSUklJBQQkIJCSUklJBQQkIJCSUklJBQQkIJCSUklJBQQkIJCSUklJBQQkIJCSUk1A0BYVPW6MOy2wAAAABJRU5ErkJggg==\" style=\"height:75px; width:66px\" \/>iii.<img src=\"data:image\/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAAFEAAABICAYAAACOVhllAAABxUlEQVR4nO2Y247DIAwF8\/8\/TZ9YVcihBsZgVmekKIm5lExxIX2KWOY5PYD\/gCQCSCKAJAJIIoAkAkgigCQCSCKAJAJIIoAkAkgigCQCSCKAJAJIIoAkAkgigCQCXCHxeR73cWR8Rz7VwYi404LTSew9eBt7qzPSJzJmvMcF2gedEdkTFSUyjUTv7LNiMyJJUkgcnX1W7KTIdBKt+15stJ+3tiscl0imsbdOLz5DCon1fEIkwVGJK2k8utXxbodmOCZxJY2t2KxYglCJ7SbX2vSuiuzV8dwThEm0Zlr07PPUab9AghCJ1oyzyj2xX21XRKaVuLLF8Ij11ptdsWcIl\/gWq\/GZtkSqXyExUpA31qtDCSwlSGI9ZxR5lcR6vUPQzEGC9jaywnrb9tLxtLy\/MeEdDv7A\/4pHpyLBloVlReSOmbRKqERaZFZC03l2AfmOZxdYSuBrXz0TIrMT+u7cXlvlb7FbBJay4V+c9toqb2M3CSwlUGIp9p7OKrfq30T4aHsid26II9k24hNvEru4e\/RJkEQASQSQRABJBJBEAEkEkEQASQSQRABJBJBEAEkEkEQASQSQRABJBJBEAEkEkEQASQT4AN+JhiXS9XldAAAAAElFTkSuQmCC\" \/>iv. <img src=\"data:image\/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAAF8AAABKCAYAAADdV4jdAAABgklEQVR4nO3Z0U6EMBQGYd7\/pY9XJIQsKYXa+bs7k3jharbHr40gbmVYGz3ALyc+mPhg4oOJDyY+mPhg4oOJDyY+mPhg4oOJDyY+mPhg4oOJDyY+mPhg4oOJDxaPv21b82PVoidvAa++CbET96KuuAlxk75BXG0DoqYchbfKBsRMOOLEt15LK2K6T\/A9cFcbl74B+GRX8E8utr1fo0Onap3YUWjif1p80qkU\/7zwRHjxj4tOBBH\/uOBkDPH3xR5cSFvff+c9xa9np3AUfuIGTMc\/fz4C7g5s4gZMm2bG\/fzdGVI2AcXfX5\/ZT+Mn\/PAJM1SBt5o9\/6EasXFXz4\/I8L9wex+ovbljEv88wIOT3fv4+PzeCfBVAfhPevPsPgW+alH8qv7f4SkX+2M5k3TWe9LT4Ku+GD8ZfS9zqpv9xy3pzPInvNEq2OfWm\/iLEh9MfDDxwcQHEx9MfDDxwcQHEx9MfDDxwcQHEx9MfDDxwcQHEx9MfDDxwcQHEx9MfDDxwf4ADOgL1YpLgVsAAAAASUVORK5CYII=\" \/><\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>From the diagram above, the effect of solidity is best exhibited in?<\/p>","options":["iii","i","iv","ii"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"2018"},{"question":"<p>Which of the following grades of pencils is good for making marks?<\/p>","options":["4B","2H","4H","HB"],"answerIndex":1,"examYear":"2018"},{"question":"<p>Artworks that are produced to serve a utilitarian purpose are classified as?<\/p>","options":["theatre arts","liberal arts","applied arts","fine arts"],"answerIndex":3,"examYear":"2018"},{"question":"<p>The Zaria Art School is known for its<\/p>","options":["motif design","natural synthesis","unnatural synthesis","freedom of expression"],"answerIndex":4,"examYear":"2018"},{"question":"<p>Literary art involves<\/p>","options":["poetry and prose","drama","architecture","painting and sculpture"],"answerIndex":1,"examYear":"2018"},{"question":"<p>A permanent pattern made on the skin is called<\/p>","options":["graffito","body painting","body design","tatoo"],"answerIndex":4,"examYear":"2018"},{"question":"<p>Which of the following supports was used by Roman painters for expression?<\/p>","options":["Walls","Canvas","Metal panels","Wooden panels"],"answerIndex":4,"examYear":"2018"},{"question":"<p>Ikogosi Warm Spring is decribed as a natural phenomenon because it<\/p>","options":["occurs naturally in the wet season","occurs naturally","is artificially kept warm","is naturally warm in the dry season"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"2018"},{"question":"<p>Which of the following towns is famous for the production of calabash?<\/p>","options":["Jos","Nok","Oyo","Benin"],"answerIndex":3,"examYear":"2018"},{"question":"<p>In corel draw application, ruler guide is used to get the<\/p>","options":["accurate size of a given object","lower size of a given object","top size of a given object","inaccurate size of a given object"],"answerIndex":1,"examYear":"2018"},{"question":"<p>The Egyptian sculptural piece that is hald animal is the<\/p>","options":["Nefetiti","Masteba","Sphinx","Mummy"],"answerIndex":3,"examYear":"2018"},{"question":"<p>Calligraphy pen can be preserved after use by<\/p>","options":["steaming in hot water","oiling","greasing","rinsing in cold water"],"answerIndex":4,"examYear":"2018"},{"question":"<p>The starch used for designing in adire-eleko is boiled with<\/p>","options":["indigo dye and white alum","yellow dye and white alum","red dye and white alum","green dye and white alum"],"answerIndex":1,"examYear":"2018"},{"question":"<p>The Mbari artists were mainly based in<\/p>","options":["Esie","Oshogbo","Lagos","Ibadan"],"answerIndex":4,"examYear":"2018"},{"question":"<p>Mosaic art of decoration was introduced during the<\/p>","options":["Romanesque period","Gothic period","prehistoric period","Medieval period"],"answerIndex":1,"examYear":"2018"},{"question":"<p>Emphasis in a composition, means that attention is drawn to<\/p>","options":["the entire surface of the composition","certain parts than others","colour harmony","colours predominantly used"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"2018"},{"question":"<p>Plasticine is an art medium that can be used in place of<\/p>","options":["wood","ivory","mud","clay"],"answerIndex":4,"examYear":"2018"},{"question":"<p>The effect produced by the combination of light, shape and colour is<\/p>","options":["shading","painting","plating","serigraphy"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"2018"},{"question":"<p>i.&nbsp; <img src=\"data:image\/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAAFcAAABhCAYAAACj6z3cAAABf0lEQVR4nO3XUWrDMBAGYd0fesFcRn0pRrg21CGj\/aXOgF+9ux8h4NYNq1UvsHPigokLJi6YuGDigokLJi6YuGDigokLJi6YuGDigokLJi6YuGDigokLJi6YuGDigokLJi6YuGDigokLJi6YuGDigokLJi6YuGDigi2D21q7fJLL3u6nO9h05Mythv4Cmwqct9HQE1hxH\/YUNw04a5tT4oKJCyYunLhwqwLnbHLRO38LSdBxuJ8ATcGOwaVRK5AjcGfDzgIux62CnQFcilsNSwOX4VaDbotbjSnuBsDTcasRxRX3zYEBkDNgexd3L9zes4DRO9G33w0NQKVhe\/\/HHxFTbpwy5W74pqjHfVOnXS2wIepxW8nUU7uhHneVTj+1A+hYziZDK4OOZW7V+y+0FTDPrbHlookLJi6YuGDigokLJi6YuGDigokLJi6YuGDigokLJi6YuGDiUr2+xCUTF0xcMHHBxAUTF0xcMHHBQNwX9+pF8pcLJi6YuGDign0DzfCUYk98EEwAAAAASUVORK5CYII=\" style=\"height:95px; width:85px\" \/>&nbsp;&nbsp; ii. <img src=\"data:image\/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAAFIAAABLCAYAAADj9dDIAAABV0lEQVR4nO3ZwQ6CMBAA0f7\/T9eTxhiJirPbXTqTcPAALS8kFjqmIY3VE7hKQkIJCSUklJBQQkIJCSUklJBQQkIJCSUklJBQQkIJCSUkVGvIMcbjWN36GZzsGbACZmvI198rMVtCHqGtxGwH+QlrFWYryG+RVmC2gfwVR8g3nX3CMjHbQJ49LwuzPOS\/GFmYpSEphAzMspD0zUdjloSMuunId\/NykOFPzk6QGWPQ45SCTF2uXBlyzrxFtJDQGEJCY2wBGb543uFfe86cJRB+TfyKQJGQ26wj70W+3US0FWTokx5yVaiIDxdRlYacs8+ntPKQc\/b4uNsKsvKWQwvIe2dA3Go46Ne9bTe\/PvQMdXSkzid1tKBWAj7msGTUCyYklJBQQkIJCSUklJBQQkIJCSUklJBQQkIJCSUklJBQQkIJCSUklJBQQkIJCSUklJBQQkIJCSUk1A0BYVPW6MOy2wAAAABJRU5ErkJggg==\" style=\"height:75px; width:66px\" \/>iii.<img src=\"data:image\/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAAFEAAABICAYAAACOVhllAAABxUlEQVR4nO2Y247DIAwF8\/8\/TZ9YVcihBsZgVmekKIm5lExxIX2KWOY5PYD\/gCQCSCKAJAJIIoAkAkgigCQCSCKAJAJIIoAkAkgigCQCSCKAJAJIIoAkAkgigCQCXCHxeR73cWR8Rz7VwYi404LTSew9eBt7qzPSJzJmvMcF2gedEdkTFSUyjUTv7LNiMyJJUkgcnX1W7KTIdBKt+15stJ+3tiscl0imsbdOLz5DCon1fEIkwVGJK2k8utXxbodmOCZxJY2t2KxYglCJ7SbX2vSuiuzV8dwThEm0Zlr07PPUab9AghCJ1oyzyj2xX21XRKaVuLLF8Ij11ptdsWcIl\/gWq\/GZtkSqXyExUpA31qtDCSwlSGI9ZxR5lcR6vUPQzEGC9jaywnrb9tLxtLy\/MeEdDv7A\/4pHpyLBloVlReSOmbRKqERaZFZC03l2AfmOZxdYSuBrXz0TIrMT+u7cXlvlb7FbBJay4V+c9toqb2M3CSwlUGIp9p7OKrfq30T4aHsid26II9k24hNvEru4e\/RJkEQASQSQRABJBJBEAEkEkEQASQSQRABJBJBEAEkEkEQASQSQRABJBJBEAEkEkEQASQT4AN+JhiXS9XldAAAAAElFTkSuQmCC\" \/>iv. <img src=\"data:image\/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAAF8AAABKCAYAAADdV4jdAAABgklEQVR4nO3Z0U6EMBQGYd7\/pY9XJIQsKYXa+bs7k3jharbHr40gbmVYGz3ALyc+mPhg4oOJDyY+mPhg4oOJDyY+mPhg4oOJDyY+mPhg4oOJDyY+mPhg4oOJDxaPv21b82PVoidvAa++CbET96KuuAlxk75BXG0DoqYchbfKBsRMOOLEt15LK2K6T\/A9cFcbl74B+GRX8E8utr1fo0Onap3YUWjif1p80qkU\/7zwRHjxj4tOBBH\/uOBkDPH3xR5cSFvff+c9xa9np3AUfuIGTMc\/fz4C7g5s4gZMm2bG\/fzdGVI2AcXfX5\/ZT+Mn\/PAJM1SBt5o9\/6EasXFXz4\/I8L9wex+ovbljEv88wIOT3fv4+PzeCfBVAfhPevPsPgW+alH8qv7f4SkX+2M5k3TWe9LT4Ku+GD8ZfS9zqpv9xy3pzPInvNEq2OfWm\/iLEh9MfDDxwcQHEx9MfDDxwcQHEx9MfDDxwcQHEx9MfDDxwcQHEx9MfDDxwcQHEx9MfDDxwf4ADOgL1YpLgVsAAAAASUVORK5CYII=\" \/><\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>The illustration reflects contrast of<\/p>","options":["tone and size","size and texture","shape and size","tone and shape"],"answerIndex":4,"examYear":"2018"},{"question":"<p>The famous artist who worked with Suzanne Wenger was<\/p>","options":["Twin Seven Seven","Ulli Beier","Jimoh Buraimoh","Jimoh Akolo"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"2018"},{"question":"<p>The annual Igwe Festival is celebrated in<\/p>","options":["Benin","Akure","Ondo","Warri"],"answerIndex":1,"examYear":"2018"},{"question":"<p>The design above is composed of<\/p>","options":["elliptical forms","elliptical shapes","basic shapes","basic forms"],"answerIndex":3,"examYear":"2018"},{"question":"<p>Architecture, an important feature of the built environment, is an example of<\/p>","options":["Literary Art","Coptic Art","Visual Art","Performing Art"],"answerIndex":3,"examYear":"2018"},{"question":"<p>A work of art is successful if the<\/p>","options":["elements are well organized","colours are sharp","surface is bright","work is monumental"],"answerIndex":1,"examYear":"2018"},{"question":"<p>An abstract art is a realistic representation of<\/p>","options":["distorted representation of an art","still life drawings","drawing of human figures","nature"],"answerIndex":1,"examYear":"2018"}]